const qBank = [
  {
    question:
      "Who invented C Language.?   ",
    answers: ["Charles Babbage","Grahambel","Dennis Ritchie","Steve Jobs"],
    correct: "Dennis Ritchie",
    questionId: "099099"
  },
  {
    question:
      'C Language is a successor to which language.?',
    answers: ["FORTRAN","D Language","BASIC","B Language"],
    correct: "B Language",
    questionId: "183452"
  },
  {
    question:
      "C is a which level language.?",
    answers: ["Low Level","High Level","Low + High","None"],
    correct: "High Level",
    questionId: "267908"
  },
  {
    question: "Low level language is .?",
    answers: [
      "Human readable like language",
      "language with big program size",
      "language with small program size",
      "Difficult to understand and readability is questionable."
    ],
    correct: "Difficult to understand and readability is questionable.",
    questionId: "333247"
  },
  {
    question: "High level language is a .?s?",
    answers: ["Human readable like language",
    "language with big program size",
    "language with small program size",
    "Difficult to understand and readability is questionable."],
    correct: "Human readable like language",
    questionId: "496293"
  },
  {
    question:
      "C is _______ type of programming language.?",
    answers: [
      "Object Oriented",
      "Procedural",
      "Bit level language",
      "Functional"
    ],
    correct: "Procedural",
    questionId: "588909"
  },
  {
    question:
      'What is the present C Language Standard.?',
    answers: ["C99 ISO/IEC 9899:1999","C11 ISO/IEC 9899:2011","C05 ISO/IEC 9899:2005","C10 ISO/IEC 9899:2010"],
    correct: "C11 ISO/IEC 9899:2011",
    questionId: "648452"
  },
  {
    question: "C language was invented in which laboratories.?",
    answers: ["Uniliver Labs","IBM Labs","AT&T Bell Labs","Verizon Labs"],
    correct: "AT&T Bell Labs",
    questionId: "786649"
  },
  {
    question:
      "BCPL Language is also called..?",
    answers: ["C Language", "B Language", "D Language", "None"],
    correct: "None",
    questionId: "839754"
  },
  {
    question:
      "C language was invented to develop which Operating System.? ",
    answers: [
      "Android",
      "Linux",
      "Ubuntu",
      "Unix"
    ],
    correct: "Unix",
    questionId: "98390"
  },
  {
    question: "C language was invented in the year.?",
    answers: ["1962", "1982", "1972", "1990"],
    correct: "1972",
    questionId: "1071006"
  },
  {
    question: "C language is used in the development of .?",
    answers: ["Databases", "Graphic Applications", "Word Processors", "All of the above"],
    correct: "All of the above",
    questionId: "1174154"
  },
  {
    question: "A C program is a combination of.?",
    answers: ["Statements", "Functions", "Variables", "All of the above"],
    correct: "All of the above",
    questionId: "1226535"
  },
  {
    question: "Single Line Comment // is also called.?",
    answers: ["C++ Style Comment", "Java Style Comment", "PHP Style Comment", "All of the above"],
    correct: "All of the above",
    questionId: "1310938"
  },
  {
    question: "What is the number of characters used to distinguish Identifier or Names of Functions and Global variables.?    ",
    answers: ["31", "32", "33", "28"],
    correct: "31",
    questionId: "1436873"
  },
  {
    question: "An Identifier can start with.?",
    answers: ["Alphabet", "_Underscore", "Any Character", "Option A&B"],
    correct: "Option A&B",
    questionId: "1515110"
  },
  {
    question: "Find an integer constant.",
    answers: ["19", "20.45", '"12"', "None"],
    correct: "19",
    questionId: "1642728"
  },
  {
    question:"Find a Floating Point constant.",
    answers: ["12.3E5","12e34","125.34857","All the above"],
    correct: "All the above",
    questionId: "1747256"
  },
  {
    question:
      "Number of Keywords present in C Language are .?",
    answers: ["32", "34", "62", "64"],
    correct: "32",
    questionId: "1822532"
  },
  {
    question: "Each statement in a C program should end with.?",
    answers: [
      "Period . ",
      "Colon : ",
      "SemiColon ; ",
      "None"
    ],
    correct: "SemiColon ; ",
    questionId: "195075"
  },
  {
    question: 'Find a correct C Keyword below.',
    answers: ["breaker", "go to", "shorter", "default"],
    correct: "default",
    questionId: "2019778"
  },
  {
    question: "Types of Real numbers in C are.?    ",
    answers: ["float", "double", "long double", "All the above"],
    correct: "All the above",
    questionId: "2134343"
  },
  {
    question: "Size of a Turbo C C++ compiler is.?",
    answers: [
      "16 Bit",
      "32 Bit",
      "64 Bit",
      "128 Bit"
    ],
    correct: "16 Bit",
    questionId: "2210799"
  },
  {
    question:
      "Sizes of short, int and long in a Turbo C C++ compiler in bytes are.?      ",
    answers: ["2,2,4", "2,4,4", "4,8,16", "8,8,16"],
    correct: "2,2,4",
    questionId: "2379831"
  },
  {
    question: "Find a C Storage Class below.",
    answers: ["static", "auto", "register & extern", "All the above"],
    correct: "All the above",
    questionId: "2426418"
  },
  {
    question: "What is the default C Storage Class for a variable.?",
    answers: ["static", "auto", "register", "extern"],
    correct: "auto",
    questionId: "2510086"
  },
  {
    question: "A register variable is stored in a Register. Where does a Register Present in a Computer.?",
    answers: [
      "RAM",
      "ROM",
      "CPU",
      "DMA"
    ],
    correct: "CPU",
    questionId: "2685745"
  },
  {
    question:
      "Variables of type auto, static and extern are all stored in .?",
    answers: ["ROM", "RAM", "CPU", "DMA"],
    correct: "RAM",
    questionId: "2796884"
  },
  {
    question: "Which among the following is a Local Variable.?",
    answers: ["register", "auto", "static", "extern"],
    correct: "auto",
    questionId: "2838900"
  },
  {
    question: 'Operator % in C Language is called.?    ',
    answers: ["Percentage Operator", "Quotient Operator", "Modulus", "Division"],
    correct: "Modulus",
    questionId: "298060"
  },
  {
    question: "Choose a C Conditional Operator from the list.",
    answers: ["?:", ":?", ":<", "<:"],
    correct: "?:",
    questionId: "3096579"
  },
  {
    question: "What is the other name for C Language ?: Question Mark Colon Operator.?    ",
    answers: [
      "Comparison Operator",
      "If-Else Operator",
      "Ternary Operator",
      "Binary operator"
    ],
    correct: "Ternary Operator",
    questionId: "3182461"
  },
  {
    question: "Loops in C Language are implemented using.?",
    answers: [
      "While Block",
      "For Block",
      "do While Block",
      "All"
    ],
    correct: "All",
    questionId: "3239112"
  },
  {
    question: "Which loop is faster in C Language, for, while or Do While.?    ",
    answers: ["while", "for", "do while", "All work at same speed"],
    correct: "All work at same speed",
    questionId: "3318503"
  },
  {
    question:
      'What is the way to suddenly come out of or Quit any Loop in C Language.?',
    answers: ["continue;", "break;", "leave;", "quit;"],
    correct: "break;",
    questionId: "3410327"
  },
  {
    question: "A function which calls itself is called a ___ function.",
    answers: ["Self Function", "Auto Function", "Recursive Function", "Static Function"],
    correct: "Recursive Function",
    questionId: "3542596"
  },
  {
    question: "What are types of Functions in C Language.?",
    answers: ["Library Function", "User Defined Function", "Both", "None"],
    correct: "Both",
    questionId: "3667517"
  },
  {
    question: "Every C Program should contain which function.?",
    answers: [
      "printf()",
      "getch()",
      "scanf()",
      "main()"
    ],
    correct: "main()",
    questionId: "3791672"
  },
  {
    question: "What is the minimum number of functions to be present in a C Program.?",
    answers: ["1", "2", "3", "4"],
    correct: "1",
    questionId: "3893585"
  },
  {
    question: 'Arguments passed to a function in C language are called ___ arguments.',
    answers: ["Formal Arguments", "Actual Arguments", "Definite Arguments", "Ideal Arguments"],
    correct: "Actual Arguments",
    questionId: "3913430"
  },
  {
    question: "Arguments received by a function in C language are called ___ arguments.    ",
    answers: ["Formal Arguments", "Actual Arguments", "Definite Arguments", "Ideal Arguments"],
    correct: "Formal Arguments",
    questionId: "4049121"
  },
  {
    question:
      "Choose a non Library C function below.",
    answers: ["printf()", "scanf()", "fprintf()", "fcprint()"],
    correct: "fcprint()",
    questionId: "4150746"
  },
  {
    question:
      "What is the default return value of a C function if not specified explicitly.?",
    answers: ["-1", "0", "1", "None"],
    correct: "1",
    questionId: "4235063"
  },
  {
    question: "A recursive function can be replaced with __ in c language.",
    answers: ["for", "while", "do while", "All"],
    correct: "All",
    questionId: "4321002"
  },
  {
    question: "A recursive function without If and Else conditions will always lead to.?",
    answers: [
      "Finite Loop",
      "Infinite Loop",
      "Incorrect result",
      "Correct result"
    ],
    correct: "Infinite Loop",
    questionId: "4442286"
  },
  {
    question: "What is the C keyword that must be used to achieve expected result using Recursion.?    ",
    answers: [
      "printf",
      "scanf",
      "return",
      "void"
    ],
    correct: "return",
    questionId: "4564430"
  },
  {
    question: "An array Index starts with.?",
    answers: ["1", "0", "-1", "2"],
    correct: "0",
    questionId: "4630606"
  },
  {
    question:
      "If an integer array pointer is incremented, how many bytes will be skipped to reach next element location.?",
    answers: ["1", "2", "8", "None"],
    correct: "2",
    questionId: "4795960"
  },
  {
    question: "An entire array is always passed by ___ to a called function.",
    answers: ["Call by Value", "Call by Reference", "Address Relocation", "Address restructure"],
    correct: "Call by Reference",
    questionId: "4811162"
  },
  {
    question: "What is the function used to allocate memory to an array at run time with Zero initial value to each.?",
    answers: ["calloc()", "malloc()", "palloc()", "kalloc()"],
    correct: "calloc()",
    questionId: "4982981"
  }
];

export default (n = 5) =>
  Promise.resolve(qBank.sort(() => 0.5 - Math.random()).slice(0, n));
